A Guide to the Marching Royal Dukes Records, 1975-2016: UA 0016
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Photographs, 1975-2016; Series 3
  - Photographs (folder 22 of 22), undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Negatives (folder 1 of 3), 1982-1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Negatives (folder 2 of 3), 1982-1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Negatives (folder 3 of 3), 1982-1999 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Media, 1975-2016; Series 4
  Series 4: Media, 1975-2016, consists of 566 pieces of recorded or saved media ranging from LP Records, 3mm tape reel recordings, camcorder tapes, VHS, CD, and DVD from 41 years of the group's existence. The content of the media is primarily audio-video recordings of the Marching Royal Dukes in performance at football games and competitions or professional audio recordings. Also included in the media are recorded performances by the JMU Pep Band, JMU Wind Symphony, and JMU Concert Band. A small portion of the media are administrative files stored on DVD-ROM ranging from 2014-2016. The MRD Official CDs, LPs, and Cassette recordings are also stored with media, ranging from 1983-2011.
  This series remains in process. Individual items may be digitized upon request. A complete inventory and detailed descriptions of individual materials is available here.
- Oversize, 1989-2001; Series 5
  The Oversize series consists of materials that do not fit within standard sized boxes and have been physically removed from their intellectual arrangement. As such, the Oversize series functions only as a container list. The following folder titles are each represented elsewhere in the collection.
  - Parade of Champions Illustration, 1989 (Box OV 1, Folder 1)
  - Clinton Inaugural Address, 1997 (Box OV 1, Folder 2)
  - Drill (folder 1 of 3), undated (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Drill (folder 2 of 3), undated (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Drill (folder 3 of 3), undated (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1991, undated (Box OV 1, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 2001 (Case Map 1:2, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Case Map 1:2, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, undated (Case Map 1:3, Folder 3)